I added support for
images yeah but even
that took hours So
I was at the
typing indicator and
then the responded
And I very vividly
remember the situation I
was standing there and
I was like how
did you do that
And the replied I'm
not kidding you the
mad lad figured it
out on its own
And then it
walked me through every
single step How it
got a from me
but there was no
file ending So it
the file It found
that it was audio
but a format so
it it And then
it was looking for
something to the
but I didn't have
it But then it
found an OpenAI key
It sent the whole
thing to the It
got it back and
then it All of
that in nine seconds
Can you imagine